owndrives.com 2017-12-16

# OwnDrives - Your Own Digital Drive - Easy way to share your files

## Privacy Policy

  * Your privacy is important to us. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and disclose Personal Information and Usage Data when you use the OwnDrives online file hosting service ("Service"). This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing your information and your preferences.

This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time. By using the Service, you agree to be bound and to abide by the most recent version of this Privacy Policy. 

### Information We Collect and How We Collect It:

  * #### Personal Information

You can use certain features of the Service without providing us with any information that identifies or may be used to directly identify you ("Personal Information"). We collect certain Personal Information when you register with OwnDrives, including your username, e-mail address, and payment information (i.e., a third party payment processor identifier). We may collect other Personal Information if you become an Reseller or use certain features of the Service. We collect Personal Information only if you choose to share it with us. The decision to provide this information is optional. However, if you choose not provide the requested information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Service. 
  * #### Usage Data

We automatically collect usage information that does not directly identify an individual user ("Usage Data"). For example, each time you use the Service we may automatically collect the type of Web browser you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider, your IP address, the links you use, and the time and duration of your use of the Service. We use this Usage Data to help us understand how people use the Service, and to enhance the services we offer. None of this information can be used to directly identify you, and we will not use it for the purpose of attempting to identify you. Please be aware, however, that we may be required to disclose information such as your IP address (a unique numerical identifier for your computer that may or may not change over time) which could be used by others to attempt to identify you. 
  * #### Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies (a small text file placed on your computer to identify your computer and Web browser when you use the Service). We may also use Web beacons (an electronic file placed on a website that monitors usage). We do not use cookies or Web beacons to collect Personal Information. We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Service. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Service may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Some of our Service Providers, as discussed below, may use their own cookies or Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf. 
  * #### Storage of Information

The information OwnDrives collects about you and your usage of the Service will be transmitted to and stored by OwnDrives on servers. 

### How We Use Information and When We May Share Information:

  * #### Generally

We generally use Personal Information only for purposes of providing and communicating with you about the Service, including responding to your requests, making payments, notifying you of new products or services, and otherwise communicating with you about the Service. We will not disclose Personal Information to third parties without your consent, except as explained in this Privacy Policy. 
  * #### Service Providers

From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses whom we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide services such as payment processing, maintenance and support, data storage and management, advertising, and marketing. We provide our Service Providers with only the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each Service Provider must agree to use reasonable security procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Service Providers are prohibited from using Personal Information other than as specified by OwnDrives.

Ad Networks. We may work with third-party advertising and marketing companies ("Ad Networks"). These companies may collect and use information about your use of the Service in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Advertisements may be shown via the Services, or third-party websites. These companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons to collect information about your use of the Service and of other Internet services and websites. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any collection or use of information about you by any Ad Network. It also does not cover any information that you may choose to provide to an Ad Network or to an advertiser whose goods or services are advertised through the Service. For more information about collection and use of information by Ad Networks. 

  * #### Data Retention

We will hold your Personal Information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity. If you cancel your registration and your account is deleted OwnDrives will no longer use the Personal Information, but for administration purposes it will stay on our system for a period of one year before being deleted. 
  * #### Security

OwnDrives is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ reasonable physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet or other network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect information transmitted on or through the Service, we cannot and do not guarantee the security of any information you upload, store, share, transmit, or provide on or through the Service, and you do so at your own risk. 
  * #### Links To Content and to Other Websites

Our Service permits users to share links to materials stored on servers owned by or operated on behalf of OwnDrives. Our Service may also contain links to other websites, or allow others to send you such links. The use of the Service to provide a link to material on OwnDrives servers or to a third party's website does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated with it. We do not exercise control over the content uploaded and shared using the Service (except that we may remove or disable access to it upon receipt of proper notice under our Intellectual Property and Rights Policy). We also do not exercise control over third-party websites. You access such content or third-party websites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third-party website before providing any information to the operator of the website. 
  * #### Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 18. By using our Services, you promise that you are at least 18 years old. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 18, we will terminate any account that user may have with OwnDrives. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from a child under the age of 18, we will delete such information from our records.
